繼續跟自己說你就是應該
Keep telling yourself that you're the one
而我想你也認為自己該多管
And I'm sure that you believe there's something left to run
噢，不要打破我的氣氛
Oh, don't kill my vibe
自從上次感到快活已過好久
'Cause it's been so long since I felt alive
而我也懶得管你想啥
And I couldn't care less what you think
因為那就是我跟我朋友的魔法
'Cause that's the magic I've got for myself and my friends
而我也懶得管你說啥
And I couldn't care less what you say
因為 Equestria 對我們兩個還是太窄
'Cause Equestria's too small for the two of us
而我也懶得管你想啥
And I couldn't care less what you think
因為那就是我跟我朋友的魔法
'Cause that's the magic I've got for myself and my friends
而我也懶得管你說啥
And I couldn't care less what you say
因為 Equestria 對我們兩個還是太窄
'Cause Equestria's too small for the two of us
路上哪裡都是麻煩，你懂？
Nothing but trouble down the bend, you know?
（你懂？）
(you know?)
一直都是這樣
It's always been like that
（都是這樣）
(been like that)
我原本在你來之前活得很好
I was living my best life till you stepped right in
（很好）
(right in)
現在我比以前都還要更好
Now I'm living better than ever before
（還要更好）
(ever before)
珍惜、寶貝一切
Live out, love out what you can
這世界不是用魔法就解決
This isn't a world solved by magic
誰都有一兩次機會
We all get a chance or two
但說夠就夠，我只是需要你
But enough is enough, I just need you
而我也懶得管你想啥
And I couldn't care less what you think
因為那就是我跟我朋友的魔法
'Cause that's the magic I've got for myself and my friends
而我也懶得管你說啥
And I couldn't care less what you say
因為 Equestria 對我們兩個還是太窄
'Cause Equestria's too small for the two of us
而我也懶得管你想啥
And I couldn't care less what you think
因為那就是我跟我朋友的魔法
'Cause that's the magic I've got for myself and my friends
而我也懶得管你說啥
And I couldn't care less what you say
因為 Equestria 對我們兩個還是太窄
'Cause Equestria's too small for the two of us